Lawrence Guyot, Jr. 130
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - North Capitol Neighborhood Development, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Loose Printed Material, 1999-2007 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1999- 2007 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Adivisory Neighborhood Commission, 1989 -2001 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Columbia Heights (1 of 2), 1998 - 2007 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Columbia Heights (2 of 2), 1999 - 2007 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1994-2004 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Resolution 14-494: Vote on D.C. Office of the District Attorney, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1999-2002 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Georgetown University, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights 1 of 3, 2000-2002 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights 2 of 3, 2000-2002 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights 3 of 3, 2000-2002 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Columbia Heights, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Howard University/LeDroit Park, 1998-2011 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Loose Correspondence, 1969-2011 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Newsclippings, 1994-2011 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Magazines, 2006-2009 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Re-Elect Commissioner Larwrence Guyot Flyers, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Flyers, 1996-2007 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Informational Handouts, 2003-2011 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Paul Robeson: Voice of the People Student Learning Activities, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Institute of African American Affairs International Synposium, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Public Welfare Foundation Annual Report, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Washington District of Columbia: Business Gateway to the World, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Supreme Court Case Number 08-322, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Committee of Economic Development, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - District of Columbia Public Schools, 1995-2001 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - National Rural Housing Coalition, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - National Rainbow Coalition Inc., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Coalition for the Homeless, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Appreciation Dinner for Lawrence Guyot Program, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Edward Kennedy - Voter Registration Bill Correspondence, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 1964-2001 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Author's Preface to the 25th Anniversary Edition of And We Are Not Saved, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Report on the National Association of Secretaries of State, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Testimony about the Voting Rigths Act, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - HistoryMakers, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Council of the Distctrict of Columbia, 1995-2007 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Board of Zoning Press Release, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2001-2008 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - LeDroit Park Civic Association, 2002-2009 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Ward 1, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Columbia Heights, 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Flyers, 2000-2007 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Informational Handouts, 1999-2004 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers, 1999-2009 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - US Black Engineer Information Technology, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Newsclippings, 2002-2009 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Press Releases, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Pamphlets - Brochures, 1999-2009 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Corresponence, 1998-2008 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Newsletters, 1996-2002 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - 4th Annual Conference of the Veterans of the Mississippi Civil Rights Movement, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - The State of Children in America's Union, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Africana Heritage, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 81st Annual Black History Lunchoen Program, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - United Neighborhods Initiative for Action Leadership Institute, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - The African-American Preadolescent Sex-Role Perception and Gender-Based Bullying Project, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Kemet Nu Productions Videotapes Information, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Blue Skies Inc. Grant Proposal, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Amicus Curiae Brief, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Drawer Content List, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Mississippi Civil Rights Movement, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Youth Vote Coallition, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - D.C. Rape Crisis Center; Project PEP HIV Post-Exposure Prophylaxis Grant Request, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Hope VI: Transforming Public Housing in the District of Columbia, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - D.C. Presidential Primary Election, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Zoning to Create Affordable Housing: Proceedings of the Forum on Affordable Housing, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Old Children's Hospital Site Redevelopment, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Jury Duty, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - MetroVoice Information Network, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Supreme Court Case: Reverend Griffen S. Smith vs Board of Elections for the District of Columbia, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 1996-2002 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Masonic Lodge Membership Card - Poker Chip, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Terminate/Reassignment Form, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Education/Schools, 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Traffic Control Plan for Langston Lofts, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Legal Documents, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Destination District, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Guide to Accessing Elected and Appointed Officials, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Howard University, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Anthony Williams, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Interview, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Voting rights, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Department of Housing and Community Development, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Regulation Administration, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Loose Programs and Brochures, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1991-2005 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - MANNA Inc., 2000-2002 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - District of Columbia Historic Presveration, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Voter Registry (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Voter Registry (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Loose Printed Material, 1991-2005 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Articles and Newspapers, 1994-2005 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - H.R. 4640, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1999-2002 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Flyers, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - 1996 Democratic National Convention (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Howard University-LeDroit Park Revitalization Initiative, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Board of Elections and Ethics, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - McMillian Sand Filtration Site, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Piernas Famliy Reunion, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Radio Business Contacts, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - United Planning Organization, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Columbia Heights Development, 1999-2003 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Informational Handouts, 2000-2005 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Newsclippings, 2001-2012 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Flyers, 1999-2012 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Magazines, 2000-2011 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Informational Booklets, 1996-2012 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Transformation: Recreating Transit-Oriented Neighborhood Centers in D.C., 2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Programs/Brochures, 1998-2012 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1985-2012 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 2000-2007 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Tivoli Theater, 1999-2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Columbia Heights Transportation Study, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Columbia Heights Ventures, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Voting Rights, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Historic Preservation Review Board Staff Report and Recommendation, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Ward One Advisory Neighborhood Council Redistricting Task Force, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1992-2001 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1 B, 1989-2005 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - DC USA, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - LeDroit Park, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Howard University, 2000-2002 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Resolution 14-494 in the Council of the District of Columbia, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Business Regulatory Reform Commission Report, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Office of Planning, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 1999-2004 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Destination Diestrict: Strategic Development Plan including Design Guidelines, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - D.C. Board of Elections and Ethics, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Federation of Civic Associations, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Department of Health, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - District of Columbia Apprenticeship Renewal Act of, 2002 2002 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Humanities Council, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Conflict Management Training, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Coalition for the Homeless, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - National Management Association Individual Membership Catalog, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - National Black Child Development Institute Inc., 2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Contact Lists, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Legacies Projects: Strategies for Making Historical Knowledge "Meaningful", 2007 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Public Hearing on Howard University Hospital Parking Garage II Construction Project, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Loose Printed Materials, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Thurgood Marshall Academy, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Student Reactions to Guyot Visit, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1999-2002 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Employment Discrimination Case, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Howard University, 2004-2007 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - LeDroit Park Civic Association, 2001-2007 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 2002-2006 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commissioners Assembly, 2000-2004 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Columbia Heights, 1999-2005 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - The Authority of Congress to Enact Legislation to Provide the District of Columbia with Voting Representation in the House of Representatives, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Department of Parks and Recreation: Banneker's Response to Confidential Draft Report, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Government of the District of Columbia Office of Planning, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 1999-2010 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1999-211 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Brochures/Pamphlets/Programs, 2005-2010 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Flyers, 2004-2008 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - D.C. Democracy Fund, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - How to Develop Difficult Neighborhood Projects, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Tips on Lobbying, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Plant Invasion in D.C., 2011 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - D.C. Board of Zoning Adjustment: St. Gertrude's School, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Press Releases, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Magazines, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Printouts of News Stories, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Newspapers and Clippings 1 of 3, 1997-2009 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Newspapers and Clippings 2 of 3, 1997-2009 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Newspapers and Clippings 3 of 3, 1997-2009 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Voter Education, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - SmokefreeDC, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - International Paper Company History, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee 50th Anniversary Conference, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Men in Childcare, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Contact List, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - International Politics Article, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - An Address by Lawrence Guyot, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Accounting Processes and Finanancial Audits, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Brookings Institute: Envisioning a Future, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Howard University: Lawrence Guyot Interview, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee Contact List, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Mail-In Voter Registration Form, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - American Friends Service Committee Southeastern Region, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Re-Elect Commissioner Lawrence Guyot Flyers, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Vote Guyot Flyers, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - District of Columbia Regulatory Refort Project, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Putting the Movement Back into Civil Rights Teaching, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Protecting Voting Rights, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Commmittee to Elect Lawrence T. Guyot Jr. Flyers, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Scholarly Papers, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Temporary Assistance for Needy Families/ 21st Century Schools Contact List, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Students Against Mass Incarceration, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 2000-2004 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B - Minutes, 2003-04-03 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B - Minutes, 2004-05-06 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B Destination District Scope, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B - Minutes, 2002-06-06 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commissioners' Assembly, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1999-2004 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission Summary/Checklist, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Columbia Heights Transportation Study Scope of Work, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Tivoli Square Fact Sheet, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Columbia Heights, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1999-2003 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Broadcast One Center, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Howard University, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 2000-2005 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - LeDroit Park, 2000-2004 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Uptown Destination District Community Work-Session: Equitable Development in Shaw, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Magazines/programs, 1987-2003 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Informational Handouts, 1996-2006 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Press Releases, 2000-2009 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Newsclippings, 1999-2004 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Flyers, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - D.C. Democracy Fund, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Freedom is a Constant Struggle Flyers, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Kathy Simo - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Correspondnce, 2001-2006 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - D.C. Board of Elections and Ethics, 2000-2004 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Office of Planning, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Board of Board of Zoning Adjustment, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Department of Human Services, 1998-2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Public Schools, 2000-2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Government of the District of Columbia, 2001-2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 1999-2001 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency Revitalization Corporation, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Charter Schools, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Health and Hospitals in D.C., 2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Advisory Commission on Sentencing, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Consumer and Regulatory Affairs, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Interfaith Conference of Metropolitan Washington, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Downtown D.C. Business Improvement District, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Report of Investigation Concerning Inadequate Oversight and Misconduct at the D.C. Board of Elections and Ethics and the Office of Campaign Finance, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Lottery Expansion Initiative of 2004 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - National Capital Revitalization Corporation, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Zoning Summary, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Euclid Street NW Draft Traffic Calming Study, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Department of Housing and Community Development, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Capital Horizon, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - 14th and U Main Street Initiative, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 2001-2003 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Programs, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Handouts and clippings, 2003-2008 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Flyers, 2002-2008 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2008 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Department of Human Resources: Offices of Early Childhood Development, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commissioners' Assembly, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1997-2002 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Empowerment Zone Briefing Packet, 1998-2002 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Woodener Apartments, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Just Vote No!, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - 18th and Vine Historic Jazz District PowerPoint Slides, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - A Work in Progress: Shaw/U Street as a Cultural Destination, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Upper Manhattan Empowerment Zone Development Corporation PowerPoint Slides, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Triangle II Development Associates LLC Development Proposal in 14th Street Urban Renewal Area, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Columbia Development L.L.C: Response to Request for Proposals: The Redevelopment of Seven Parcels in the 14th Street Urban Renewal Area 1 of 2, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Columbia Development L.L.C: Response to Request for Proposals: The Redevelopment of Seven Parcels in the 14th Street Urban Renewal Area 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - The Savoy, The Columbian, Meridian Square A Proposal by: Blair McDaniels, LLC, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commissioner Handbook, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - National Capital Revitalization Corporation, 2000-2002 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Redevelopment Land Agency, 1999-2003 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Howard University, 1997-2004 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Marion S. Barry Jr. vs Joseph E. diGenova Court Cases, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - From the desk of Guyot, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - North Capitol Neighborhood Development Inc., 2001 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Proposed Revitalizaion Plan of the National Capital Revitalization Corporation, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rethinking Schools Magazine, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Informational Handouts, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Loose Programs and Printed Material, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Counicil of the District of Columbia, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1989-2006 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Newspapers and Articles, 1986-2006 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections and Ethics, 2002-2006 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Cada Vez - U Street Corridor, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Columbia Heights Development, 1999-2006 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Superior Court of the District of Columbia, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Land Disposition and Development Agreement (1 of 2), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Land Disposition and Development Agreement (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Historical Document, 1999-2006 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - District of Columbia Redevelopment Land Agency, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Columbia Heights Renaissance Project, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Columbia Heights Renaissance Project, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Columbia Heights Renaissance Project, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Columbia Heights New Horizon Partners (1 of 4), 2001 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Columbia Heights New Horizon Partners (2 of 4), 2001 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Columbia Heights New Horizon Partners (3 of 4), 2001 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Columbia Heights New Horizon Partners (4 of 4), 2001 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 2000-2003 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1998-2004 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Columbia Heights, 1996-2000 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Development Corporation of Columbia Heights, 1996-2003 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Council of the District of Columbia, 1999-2010 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Ward 1, 1994-2001 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Government Department of Housing and Urban Development, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Board of Zoning Adjustment, 1986-2003 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Board of Ethics and Elections, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Government, 1994-2004 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Brochures/Handouts/Programs, 1995-2004 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Flyers, 1997-2003 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1996-2011 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Magazines, 2004-2009 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Ronald Regan Calendar, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - The Search for Shelter: The American Institute of Architects, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Newsclippings, 1999-2011 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases, 1997-2006 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Building Communities from Within: Empowering Neighborhood People, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Coalition for the Homeless, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Protecting Voting Rights, 2000-2005 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - The Brookings Institute, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - The District of Columbia Democratic Party Platform, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Coalition in Defense of African American Education, 1994-2006 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Empowerment Zones Briefing, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Resolution of Apology: Senate Resolution 39, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Northern Mississippi Rural Legal Services Greenville Office Correspondence, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Recognizing and Reporting Child Abuse, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - The Authority of Congress to Enact Legislation to Provide the District of Columbia with Voting Representation in the House of Representatives, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Center for Mental Health Services, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Report of the Commission on Presidential Nomination Timing and Scheduling, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Teaching for Change: Building Social Justice Starting in the Classroom, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - D.C. Metropolitan Police Department Issues, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Proposed District of Columbia Apprenticeship and Training Act of 2001 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - National Black Child Development Institute, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Thomas Pressley - Letter to the President, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Mental Health Law Project, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials, 1999-2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Carter G. Woodson Commemoration Contest, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Loose Printed Materials, 1999-2009 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 1998-2001 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 1B, 1998-2004 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Neighborhood Revitalization, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 8)